https://whale.org/privacy-policy-2/

ProgramsSnotBotDisentanglementDrones for Whale ResearchSouthern Right Whale ResearchVoyage of the OdysseyGulf of MexicoHumpback SongEducationWhale ConservationA Brief History of WhalingRobotics ClubClimate change and whalesArt & ScienceAbout UsOur HistoryInnovation CenterThe TeamCollaborationsPolicy & FinancialsPrivacy PolicyCopyrightPublicationsContact UsBlogShopWish ListAdopt a WhaleDonate
Ocean Alliance Privacy PolicyOcean Alliance has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy and protection of your information. As part of the normal operation of services, we collect and, in some instances, disclose information about you. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 1. Information Collected During Your Use of the Whale.org / Ocean Alliance website. – Certain information, such as ‘cookies’ and other related server reporting is for use in our records.2. Our Use of Your Information – We use customer contact information from the registration form to send you information about Ocean Alliance and promotional material from some of our partners. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. We may use your IP address to help protect our partners and us from fraud.3. Our Disclosure of Your Information –  We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described in this Privacy Policy and without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Ocean Alliance will never willfully sell, lease, or rent any of your or your business’ personally identifiable information to any third party.If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, please contact us at info@whale.org.Want to get more involved? find out how you can help Copyright © 2019, Ocean Alliance. All Rights Reserved.
